

□ (+60) 14-881-7836 | **>** byu1628@protonmail.com | **□** gohanko | **□** gohanko

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript ecosystem, currently writing API specs for payment systems.

Skills_____

Languages Javascript, Python

Tooling Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn, ... various other JS libaries

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy

Industry Knowledge CI/CD, Agile Software Development

Work Experience _____

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

BACKEND DEVELOPER Apr. 2020 - Present

• Building an API that directly perform operations on databases using Hapi and MSSql.

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER Dec. 2018 - Apr. 2020

- Learned the Javascript/Frontend ecosystem without prior experience or exposure.
- · Worked in a team and inter-department environment to deliver thorough and detailed work without cutting corners.
- Built and maintained large and complex code bases used by millions of people.
- Translate design and wire frames into code.
- · Maintained our legacy projects by squashing bugs, resolving security issues and perform required amendments to it.
- Participated in scrum related activities to ensure proper software development lifecycle.

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018 SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

• Implemented RESTful API server for a invoice tracking system.

- Collaborated with remote teams to deliver the product.
- Helped to implement a redesign on a social media management service.
- Built a shopify shop for a local car rental.

Projects

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Freelance

Jenexus Invoice Management System

Remote

Jun. 2017 - Aug. 2017

Remote

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

· Contracted to build the backend for an invoice management system by a software house for their client.

- In summary, it is a basic CRUD app built using Django, complete with unit tests and documentation.
- There were about 16 views/pages which does various stuff but essentially boils down to CRUD.
- Business logic is written primarily in these views, and models are kept strictly for data queries and data manipulation.
- · Tests are written using unittests which tests the views by checking its return values (status code, content in page, etc), tests are also written for models to check if our custom functions are returning the correct values.
- Deployed on an Ubuntu instance (Debian is also tested). This involved a lot of manual setup but in hindsight we could have use Docker and written scripts to automate the deployment as well as data backups. CI/CD would have been nice as well.

Education

Riam Road Secondary School

Miri, Malaysia

MALAYSIAN CERTIFICATE OF EXAMINATION

Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2016

- The Malaysian Certificate of Examination is the equivalent of the GCSE in England or GCE Ordinary Level in the Commonwealth of Nations.
- · Scored a 3A 4B in the examination which includes Mathematics (A-), Science (A), English (A), Malay (B+), Moral Studies (B+), History (B), and Art
- The English subject has 2 results, one is the MCE result and the other is the GCE Ordinary Level result, in which I scored an A as well.

BRANDON YII · RÉSUMÉ JULY 22, 2020